forexclub.biz 2019-07-17

# P

LIBERTEX | 2016
PRIVACY AND COOKIES POLICY
                    «FOREX CLUB INTERNATIONAL LIMITED» (registration No. 1529 СTD 2014)
                           The Financial Services Centre, P.O. Box 1823, Stoney Ground,
                                 Kingstown, VC0100, St. Vincent & the Grenadines
       Phone: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Fax: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Email: info@libertex.org ◦ Website: Libertex.org

LIBERTEX | 2016
PRIVACY AND COOKIES POLICY
Libertex (libertex.org) is brand name of FOREX CLUB INTERNATIONAL LIMITED (registration No. 1529 CTD 2014)
(hereinafter: “We”, “Libertex”, the “Company”). FOREX CLUB INTERNATIONAL LIMITED Offices are located at Stoney
Ground,Kingstown, VC0100, St. Vincent & the Grenadines, P.O. Box 1823, .
To help Libertex to understand the needs of its customers and improve service, data collected on this website will be
held on Libertex secure database. All customer data stored on Libertex servers complies with statutory
requirements. We will never make this data available to any other company or third party.
SECURITY
We have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy.
Libertex endeavor to protect the information you provide and ensuring that your privacy is protected and there are
strict security procedures that have been put in place. Our servers can only ever be accessed by authorised
personnel.
While we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your information, you acknowledge that the use of the internet
is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal data
transferred from you, or to you via the internet.
YOUR CONSENT
By using our website and allowing cookies on your browser which gives us access to certain information or manually
submitting your information to us you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change
our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so
that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the service will
signify that you agree to any such changes.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
When you access our website we collect non-identifiable information in the following ways:
LOG DATA
When you access our website we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or online
service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address,
browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to the Site and information you search for on the Site
and the Service. In addition, if you access the Service via a mobile device, we may collect a Push ID, subject to your
consent as indicated by you in the mobile application, and a Mobile IP.
COOKIES
Cookies are small text files stored by your browser on your computer or device when you visit certain pages or
perform certain actions on this and other websites. They are used to help your browser remember your choices and
display the correct information for you - such as items in your basket - and not treat you as a new visitor each time
you visit a page.
Some cookies are only set for the duration of your visit (“session cookies”) to help you get around and give you
relevant information. Others are set for longer periods (“persistent cookies”) so that your browser can remember
your choices from a previous visit. The cookies stored cannot harm your device, are anonymous, and unique to a
certain browser.
You can choose to disable or block these cookies in your browser but without some of them our site will not work.
For more detailed information about cookies please visit ​www.allaboutcookies.org​.
                      «FOREX CLUB INTERNATIONAL LIMITED» (registration No. 1529 СTD 2014)
                             The Financial Services Centre, P.O. Box 1823, Stoney Ground,
                                   Kingstown, VC0100, St. Vincent & the Grenadines
         Phone: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Fax: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Email: info@libertex.org ◦ Website: Libertex.org

LIBERTEX | 2016
HOW WE USE COOKIES?
At Libertex we use cookies to help us find which services you are interested in and remember details about your
application. We don't store sensitive information like your name or address in our cookies, just an anonymous
reference to them so that we're able to find them.
We also occasionally set cookies to help you navigate around the site, enhance your experience, or give you
important information regarding interests.
THIRD PARTY COOKIES
In order to give you the best possible client experience, we partner with a number of Third parties to help us collect
anonymous statistics about how our site is being used and provide you with further information that may be of
interest to you. As part of this process our Third party partners may set their own cookies during your visit.
These Third parties may include, but are not limited to, Google, Inc. (google.com/analytics/), Tealium Inc.
(tealium.com), Mixpanel, Inc. (mixpanel.com), Salesforce.com, Inc. (salesforce.com).
COOKIES SETTINGS
If you don't want to receive certain categories of cookies on the Libertex website, you can opt-out of them. We will
need to set a cookie so that we can remember your choices when you next visit the website from the same browser.
At the present time it is not technically possible for us to allow you to carry your settings with you between your
browsers and devices so you will need to change these settings from each browser you use.
Please also be aware that we make every effort to respect your choices, however, there is the possibility that not all
cookies will be captured. If this is a concern then we would recommend that you change your cookie settings via
your browser; your browser help function will tell you how.
Note: most of our website may work without cookies, but you will lose some features and functionality if you choose
to disable cookies.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
We use Google Analytics on the website, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google
Analytics is used to help us obtain data regarding use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about
your use of the website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the
United States. Google will use this information for evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website
activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google
may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties
process the information on Google’s behalf. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings
on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full website functionality.
By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes
set out above.
HOW WE USE INFORMATION
We use your information in order to (i) monitor and analyze use of the website and for the technical administration
of the website, (ii) improve the website, (iii) generate and derive useful data and information concerning the
interests, characteristics, use and behavior of our visitors.
Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information. We may share aggregated information, including queries
and offers generated as a result of your use of the website, that includes non-identifying information and Log Data,
with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, other commercial purposes and to deliver targeted
                      «FOREX CLUB INTERNATIONAL LIMITED» (registration No. 1529 СTD 2014)
                              The Financial Services Centre, P.O. Box 1823, Stoney Ground,
                                    Kingstown, VC0100, St. Vincent & the Grenadines
        Phone: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Fax: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Email: info@libertex.org ◦ Website: Libertex.org

LIBERTEX | 2016
advertising about products and services. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain any
personal information.
Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and
private parties to enforce and comply with the law.
Business Transfers. We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including among others your
Personal Information and Log Data, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of all or
substantially all of our shares or assets, or in the event of our bankruptcy.
In addition, we may post additional ancillary privacy notices with respect to specific services.
DURATION OF KEEPING INFORMATION
We will not keep your information for any longer than is required. In many cases, information must be kept for
considerable periods of time. Retention periods will be determined taking into account the type of information that
is collected and the purpose for which it is collected, bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation
and the need to destroy outdated, unused information at the earliest reasonable time.
SCOPE OF THE POLICY AND THIRD PARTY SITES
This policy applies only to us and this website. We do not exercise control over other websites, or over banners or
links from within our website. These other websites, banners or links may place their own cookies or other files on
your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you subject to such third party’s privacy policy. We
encourage you to read the privacy policies and other terms of such third parties before accessing or using them.
HOW TO CONTACT US
We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or
comments please send an e-mail to ​info@libertex.org​.
                       «FOREX CLUB INTERNATIONAL LIMITED» (registration No. 1529 СTD 2014)
                              The Financial Services Centre, P.O. Box 1823, Stoney Ground,
                                    Kingstown, VC0100, St. Vincent & the Grenadines
        Phone: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Fax: +7 (495) 727-06-06◦ Email: info@libertex.org ◦ Website: Libertex.org
